Mss.B.F865
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence
  - Letter to A[lexander] D[allas] Bache, May 23, 1863; 9-1/2x7-3/4; Davis, Charles Henry, 1807-1877
    Washington. L. 1p. Copy. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks that the national academy report on the advisability of further government aid for navigation.
  - Letter to Jo [h]n F[ries] Frazer, May 25, 1863; 8x5; Collins, Isaac
    Philadelphia, A.L.S 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...: 1834-1870) Thanks for favor.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 26, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. Enc.wanting. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Forwards letter. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], June 2, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning W.B.Rogers. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], June 2, 1863; 8x5-1/4; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A. D. Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, June 2, 1863; 10x7-3/4; Caswell, Alexis, 1799-1877
    Providence, A.L.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning the constitution of the national academy.
  - Letter to Jo[h]n F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, June 2, 1863; 10x7-3/4; Davis, Charles Henry, 1807-1877
    Washington, L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning the constitution of the national academy.
  - Letter to Cha[rle]s H[enry] Davis, June 6, 1863; 10x7-3/4; Gilliss, J. M. (James Melville), 1811-1865
    Washington, L. 3p. Copy. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Government expenses for aid for navigation.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], June 12, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    New York, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning W.B.Rogers, Gould and the national academy of sciences. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, June 12, 1863; 10x7-3/4; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.)
    Washington, L.S.: F.A.P. Barnard. 6p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning government expenditures for aid for navigation.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], June 25, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to Persifor. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], July 13, 1863; 8x5-1/4; Barnard, Frederick A. P. (Frederick Augustus Porter), 1809-1889
    Washington, A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Business.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, July 16, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Philadelphia, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning the riots in Philadelphia. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, July 18, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. News of the war. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, July 28, 1863; 8-1/4x5-1/4; Rindge, J.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Invitation.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Aug. 8, 1863; 8x5-1/4; Barnard, Frederick A. P. (Frederick Augustus Porter), 1809-1889
    Washington, A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Concerning a hydrometer.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 11, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to Jo[h]n F[ries] Frazer, Aug. 17, 1863; 7-3/4x4-3/4; McFadden, William H.
    Germantown, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1970.) Asks favor.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Sept. 14, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Bridgeport, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Sept. 19, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Bridgeport, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John Fries Frazer, October 1, 1863; Barnard, Frederick A. P. (Frederick Augustus Porter), 1809-1889
    From U.S. Coast Survey Office. Mentions hydrometer. Refers to Professor Chauvenet.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Oct. 8, 1863; 8x5; Barnard, Frederick A. P. (Frederick Augustus Porter), 1809-1889
    Washington, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to John [Fries] Frazer, Nov. 7, 1863; 8x5-1/4; Roddon, James
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks a favor.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Nov. 19, 1863; 8x5; Caswell, Alexis, 1799-1877
    Providence, A.L.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning the constitution of the national academy. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 26, 1863; 8x6; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. University of Pennsylvania business. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, 1863; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Sunday [?]. A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Concerning a boiler explosion, 1863?; 9-3/4x7-3/4; Rogers, Stephen, 1826-1878
    [ca.]. D.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers.) Correspondence...; 1834-1870.)
  - Note to [John Fries Frazer?, May, 1864; 2-1/2x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.N. 1p. (see Frazer papers Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Answers question. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Jan. 2, 1864; 8x5-1/4; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.)
    Philadelphia, L. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Informs him of meeting.
  - Telegraph to Jo[h]n F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, May 3, 1864; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, Telegram. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Asks question concerning the boiler explosion investigation. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Fairman Rogers and L[ewis] M[orris] Rutherfurd, May 4, 1864; 8x5; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.)
    Washington, A.L.S.: A.D. Bache. 2p. Enc.of 7 newspapers clippings. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning a boiler explosion. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 5, 1864; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letter from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, May 13, 1864; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, New York, May 25, 1864; 7x4-1/2; Rutherford, Lewis M.
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Business.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, New York, June 1, 1864; 8x5 and 5-1/4x3-1/2; Rutherford, Lewis M.
    New York, A.L.S. 2p.and add.with 4p.of pencil notes. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning a boiler explosion. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, June 3, 1864; 8x5; Isherwood, B. F. (Benjamin Franklin), 1822-1915
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D. Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning a boiler explosion. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, June 16, 1864; 8x5; Hilgard, J. E. (Julius Erasmus), 1825-1891
    Washington, A.L.S.1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) News of A.D.Bache.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, July 11, 1864; 8-1/4x5; Rutherford, Lewis M.
    A.L.S. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Oct. 20, 1864; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Boston, A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Nov. 12, 1864; 8x5; Crosby, Howard, 1826-1899
    A.L.S. 6p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to J[ohn Fries] Frazer, Dec. 18, 1864; 8x5; Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Agassiz, no. 18.) Formerly B F865.a. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Dec. 27, 1864; 8x5; Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Agassiz, no. 19.) Formerly B F865.a. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, March 6, 1865; 8-3/4x5-1/2; Erni, H.
    Washington, A.L.S. 3p.and add. Enc. of 5 newspaper clippings of various sizes. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks aid in getting job in the petroleum industry. Forwards clippings which he has done on petroleum.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, March 20, 1865; 8x5; Gould, Benjamin Apthorp, 1824-1896
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Refers to Rogers, Peirce, LeConte and Agassiz.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, April 2, 1865; 8x5; Gould, Benjamin Apthorp, 1824-1896
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Refers to the APS.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, April 8, 1865; 8x5; Barnard, Frederick A. P. (Frederick Augustus Porter), 1809-1889
    New york, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning grades at the university.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, May 2, 1865; 8x5; Potter, Walter McD.
    Denver, A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; Asks him to investigage mines.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], June 1, 1865; 9-3/4x7-3/4; National Academy of Sciences. (U.S.)
    Cambridge, L.S.: Wolcott Gibbs. 1p. Copy. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning changes in meeting dates.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, June 7, 1865; 8x5; Potter, Walter McD.
    Denver, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Business.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer,Newport, R.I., Aug. 31, 1865; 8x5; Hamilton, William
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Franklin institute business.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Dec. 5, 1865; 8x5; Fraley, F., (Frederick), 1804-1901
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) University business.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Jan. 27, 1866; 8x5; Fraley, F., (Frederick), 1804-1901
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Jan. 30, 1866; 8x5; Fraley, F., (Frederick), 1804-1901
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, April 30, 1866; 8x5-1/4; Alexander, J. H. (John Henry), 1812-1867
  - Note to [John Fries] F[razer], May 29, 1866; 6x8-1/4; Guillott
    A.N.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning a lightning conductor.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Oct. 13, 1866; 8x5; Guillott
    A.L.S. 3p.and enc. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Invites him to a visit and sends train schedule.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Dec. 5, 1866; 8x5; University of Pennsylvania. Trustees
    A.L.S.: Cadwalader Biddle. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Grants leave of absence.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Dec. 12, 1866; 8x5
    Philadelphia, A.L.S.: W[illia]m Sellers, Prest. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Will not accept his resignation.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Dec. 22, 1866; 10x7-3/4
    Philadelphia, A.L.S.: Henry Morton. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Accepts resignation.
  - Letter to J[ohn Fries] Frazer, Dec. 24, 1866; 8x5; Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Agassiz, no. 20.) Formerly B F865.a. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John [Fries] Frazier [sic], Feb. 11, 1867; 8x5; Morris, Caspar William
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer Papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks question.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Feb. 12, 1867; 7-3/4x4-3/4; Booth, James Curtis, 1810-1888
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning an orrery.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Feb. 14, 1867; 8x5; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    Washington, A.L.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 20.) Formerly B F865.h. Concerning the burial of A.D.Bache. Mentions the APS, University of Pennsylvania, and LeConte. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, March 1, 1867; 9-1/4x5-1/2; Alexander, V. F.
    Baltimore, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1843-1870.) Concerning the health of his father, J.H.Alexander.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, March 1, 1867; 8x5; Gould, Benjamin Apthorp, 1824-1896
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, March 5, 1867; 8x5; Bache, Hartman, 1798-1872
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...: 1834-1870.) Thanks for sympathy due to death of A.D.Bache.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, March 9, 1867; 9-3/4x7-3/4; Davidson, George, 1825-1911
    Germantown, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Astronomical observations for longitude by electricity.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, March 12, 1867; 8x5-1/4; Carson, Hiram
    Annapolis, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks to borrow publications. Refers to Haldeman.
  - Letter to [George] Davidson, March 13, 1867; 9-3/4x7-3/4; Patterson, C. P. (Carlile Pollock), 1816-1881
    Washington, A.L.S. 1p. Copy. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Frazer's recommendation to Peirce would be of aid.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, March 14, 1867; 9-3/4x7-3/4; Davidson, George, 1825-1911
    Germantown, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Philadelphia, March 19, 1867; 8x5; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 2.) Formerly B F865.h. Concerning a government appointment which should have gone to Agassiz. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, March 23, 1867; 8x5; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 3.) Formerly B F865.h. Concerning LeConte. Death of Dr. Alexander. Need for appointment to the mint. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, April 8, 1867; 8-1/4x5-1/2; Bache, Evey (Nancy Clarke Fowler)
    Newport, R.I., []. A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, April 8, 1867; 8x5; Carson, Hiram
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, April 15, 1867; 8x5; Hayes, I. I, (Isaac Israel), 1832-1881
    New York, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, April 15, 1867; 8x5; University of Pennsylvania. Trustees
    A.L.S.: Cadwalader Biddle. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Approves his request for leave of absence.
  - Letter to Benjamin Peirce, April 18, 1867; 8x5; Cooper, W. W.
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning the A.D.Bache papers at the university of Pennsylvania.
  - Letter to John Fries Frazer, April 18, 1867; Riverside Magazine for Young People.
    Refers to volume that was forwarded to Lippincott.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, April 18, 1867; 8x5; U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey
    Cambridge, L.S.: Benjamin Peirce. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) A.D.Bache papers at the university of Pennsylvania have no further information for the survey.
  - Letter to Michel Charles, April 29, 1867; 8x5; Peirce, Benjamin, 1809-1880
    Harvard, A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Introduces John F.Frazer.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, May 2, 1867; 8x5; Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Agassiz, no. 21.) Formerly B F865.a. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [whom it may concern], May 2, 1867; 8x5; Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 1p. In French. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Agassiz, no. 22.). Formerly B F865.a. Letter of introduction of Frazer. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [Sir] H[enry] W[entworth] Acland, Oxford, May 27, 1867; 8x5; Peirce, Benjamin, 1809-1880
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Introduces J.F.Frazer.
  - Letter to [Sir Edward] Sabine, May 27, 1867; 8x5; Peirce, Benjamin, 1809-1880
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 1p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Introduces J.F.Frazer. Refers to A.D. Bache.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 10, 1867; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 21.) Formerly B F865.h. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [whom it may concern], Aug. 10, 1867; 11-1/2x8; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    Washington, L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 22.) Formerly B F865.h. Introduces John Fries Frazer. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Paris, July 30, 1868; 10-1/2x8; Fraley, F., (Frederick), 1804-1901
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) University business. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Oct. 18, 1868; 8x5; Alexander, V. F.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Nov. 10, 1868; 10x7-1/2; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    Washington, L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 23.) Formerly B F865.h. Appoints him to a commission. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Nov. 16, 1868; 8x5-1/2; Gibbs, Wolcott, 1822-1908
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Jo[h]n [Fries] Frazer, Dec. 2, 1868; 8x5; Hayes, Richard Somers, ca.1847-1905.
    Paterson, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Thanks for publication.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Jan. 31, 1869; 8x5; Gould, Benjamin Apthorp, 1824-1896
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning A.D.Bache.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, April 7, 1869; 8-1/4x5-1/2; Gibbs, Wolcott, 1822-1908
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Concerning the national academy.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, April 15, 1869; 8x5; Johnson, Samuel William, 1830-1909
    New Haven, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Refers to Henry.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, May 11, 1869; 8x5; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    A.L.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 24.) Formerly B F865.h. Is working for the national academy due to the insistance of Mrs. A.D.Bache. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, June 2, 1869; 8x5; University of Pennsylvania. Trustees
    A.L.S.: Cadwalader Biddle. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning his salary.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], June 11, 1869; 8x5; Morton, Henry, 1836-1902
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning astronomical instruments.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], July 23, 1869; 8x5; Morton, Henry, 1836-1902
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks loan of astronomical instrument.
  - Letter to [E.Otis] Kendall, July 29, 1869; 8x5; Jackson, F. A.
    Germantown, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning Frazer. On same sheet is letter from Kendall to Frazer; Aug. 5, 1869.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Aug. 5, 1869; 8x5; Kendall, E. Otis (Ezra Otis), 1818-1899
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Forwards letter by Jackson. On same sheet as letter from Jackson to Kendall; July 29, 1869.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Oct. 2, 1869; 10x8; Fraley, F., (Frederick), 1804-1901
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) University business.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Dec. 5, 1869; 8x5-1/4; LeConte, John L., (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
    Algiers, A.L.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Describes Algiers. Refers to Lesley.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Jan. 7, 1870; 8x5; West, George G.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, March 20, 1870; 8-1/4x5-1/4; LeConte, John L., (John Lawrence), 1825-1883
    Algiers, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Refers to Lesley.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, March 31, 1870; 8x5; Evans, Rowland
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Notifies him that he has been excused from jury duty.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, June 6, 1870; 10-1/2x8; Rice, J. D.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning lightning and lightning rods.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Aug. 10, 1870; 9x5-1/2; Pugh, T. B.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks him to lecture with Agassiz, etc.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, Sept. 19, 1870; 8x5; Davidson, George, 1825-1911
    Victoria, V.I., A.L.S. 5p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Concerning the coast survey. Refers to LeConte.
  - Letter to John Fries Frazer, August 7, 1871; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    Refers to John Tyndall. On the custom by some prominent men, including Emerson, on lecturing for pay. (See Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 25.). Formerly B F865.h. Film 1249.